yes i am i'm an idiot i was just hoping
you'd be older than eight when you
figured that out
it all gets better it all gets different
everything's different like like where
the parents buy your applause where are
the parents with us tonight parents
can i ask how old your kids are six and
three how about here
eight months you got one oh eight months
eight months
almost here it goes the other way he's
counting in reverse eight months fema
that's negative one month is what you're
trying to tell me
we've got one that's a negative one it's
going pretty well
that's pretty cool though all right how
about older anybody i'm looking for like
grade school anybody grade school how
old
it's not like when the audience heckles
each other that's nice
you guys are old and you're stupid for
that
so you said 21 17 and 14 okay now let me
ask you this do you remember what grade
it was
where you couldn't help them with their
homework anymore do you remember when
that comes a lot sooner than we think
it's going to come doesn't it
what grade you remember
[Music]
fourth grade thanks for telling me the
truth i appreciate it i tapped out in
third i'm not one to judge anybody that
is a horrible feeling
when a third grader brings it to it
you're like let's have a look
but you're not ready to tell them that
you can't do their homework it's third
grade
so somehow you have to find your way out
of it and this is what i did if it
hasn't happened for you yet
keep this in mind when that time comes i
looked at it pretended like it made
sense he's over here and finally i just
went
well you know i i could just give you
the answers probably doesn't help you
very much
sure i could rattle them off we'd both
be done with it but that doesn't help
you
so you're an idiot aren't you yes i am
i'm an idiot i was just hoping you'd be
older than eight when you figured that
out
oh it's the worst i was were you good
students yourself are you a good student
the lady that tapped out in uh in fourth
grade
you're a teacher now
so that's why you're saying the new math
i don't like it i don't like it at all
i'm gonna
teach you the old style sit down learn
something
see i was not a good student and i
readily admit that therefore what i'm
about to tell you i'm not bragging it's
just
luck of the draw i have a really smart
son one of those kids one of those
brilliant kids
everything came easy to his whole life
but i will never forget the first bump
in the road for him
he's away at college he i shouldn't
laugh at this it was
very traumatic he calls home and i can
hear it in his voice he goes i don't
know what i'm going to do
i'm actually getting a c in one of my
classes i've never gotten a c
in my life like really that's
interesting
because you know what happened when i
was a kid and i got to see we got to go
to ponderosa all right
so i don't want to hear about your sea
and i hung up which i know is the wrong
thing to do
as soon as i did it i knew it was wrong
i called him right back i said look i'm
sorry i was trying to be funny that was
wrong i shouldn't hung up on you
i realize you're going through a tough
time and that these classes harder than
anything you've ever experienced and the
truth of the matter is i could drive
down there
and give you the answers but that really
doesn't help you at all
he said you're an idiot he hung up which
somehow made me feel better
i was not a good student i in fact i had
a.d.d before add was invented does
everybody know what i mean when i say
that
now they put these letters after a kid's
name and everybody wants to help them
where were those teachers when i was in
school
man those letters if that last letter is
a d they are all on board aren't they
of course he's staring out the window
he's got add what's he supposed to do
he's adhd he's adhd he's bd and he's ld
and on top of that i think he's ocd
when i was a kid they're like it's a
dumbass
that's pretty much how the
parent-teacher conferences went
my mom and dad you know he's a dumbass
there's really nothing we can do to help
your son he's uh
he's going to be doing these perforated
workbook pages until he's 19. so you
know what
tell him to pick out a trade college
isn't for everybody
remember that expression college isn't
for everybody if that's ever been said
to you you know what that means
it means you're not going to college
that's what it means
those of you that went away to school
remember those those weekends when you
were in high school and your parents
were taken to different schools and
you'd look at the campus remember how
great that was
my parents would take me to factories
generally on the weekends that's how i
get there
we're gonna go check out the steel bill
on saturday so keep it crossed
you can commute if you get that gig
that'll be fantastic
people think kids grow out of it they'll
teach you what is your name ma'am the
teacher
i don't have to call you mrs anderson
though right there
you're like a teacher everywhere mrs
anderson okay mrs anderson
so so um people have a misconception
about kids who don't pay attention well
and they think that when they get to be
adults they grow out of it and it's all
gone and everything's better
that's what some people think isn't it
couldn't be further from the truth could
it mrs anderson
right fact is it gets worse because the
stuff you're blowing off as an adult
is way more important than the stuff
you're not paying attention as a kid and
nobody's got your back when you're an
adult you know you're like insurance
wait what who died what no okay what
mortgage what god stop and wait there's
a fly on the road wait what stop
there's a spot on your shirt wait what
about who what now
it's the worst correct but technology
makes it way better okay i will say this
uh gps is add's greatest friend ever
invented
oh thank god for gps i'll tell you what
gps will tell you what to do every 10
seconds if you ask it to
i know that because i ask you to gps is
like in two miles turn left and one mile
turn left and a half a mile turn left
and a quarter mile turn left an eighth
of a mile turn left god you're an idiot
would you turn left i said it five times
here's something my gps said to me two
months ago said in a quarter mile
continue straight
now some people might be offended by a
command that simple i was like
yeah i was actually wondering if i
should do that because you didn't say
anything in a while
sometimes i get there like sure just
keep going then yes if i don't say
anything just keep going straight
[Music]
remember when we used to be able to pay
for gas like after we pumped it remember
those days you could pump it going i
used to forget all the time i would like
pump it and just drive off beyond my
merry way you know
now that doesn't happen anymore because
we have to pay first what i've done more
than once
pay forget to pump anyone ever do that
i'm going to be honest you don't go back
after that when you just take it on the
chin i hope there's another gas station
because there's no way i'm showing my
face in that speedway ever again
you know they're waiting for you guys
behind the counter all right if that
idiot doesn't show up in the next five
minutes
fountain drinks on the house get in line
i've got a 30
credit funny none of my kids inherited
that trade
i'm so happy about that got four and
that's a lot
i know it is because people tell me it's
a lot anybody here four or more knows
i'm talking about
people tell you have a lot of kids don't
they people their minds are boggled when
they find out somebody has more kids
than they do because in their mind they
can't figure out how that works
here's the thing that we say to me and
man what were you thinking
what were you think well we were kind of
thinking that it doesn't really affect
your life that's what i was sort of
thinking but
not really sure where you're getting so
excited about just a number
it's not like i asked you to sponsor one
of them or anything it's essentially a
single digit
you got two and two five kids what were
you
thinking wait what no wait stop what
go ahead tell me three boys two girls
okay whatever the other one is all right
got three boys and a girl in that order
so if you're a fan of game shows i
describe it this way it's like joker
joker joker i gotta pay for a wedding
right
i don't think that way
but when we were kids that wasn't a big
family i was the youngest of four
anybody or the baby the family besides
me
youngest of how many just two that older
sibling your brother
your sister did she pick on you beat you
up a little bit how many years between
the two of you
five that's a lot that's not fair right
that was my brother and me seven between
us yet he still did it i'm like how is
this exciting for you
it's like he's ten and i'm three okay
knock yourself out hercules
he's like hovering over me come on get
up
i'll kick those training pants right off
your backside
and he can still take me we're not gonna
get in a fight we're growing men but he
can still take me we both know it and
that bothers me
i keep doing the math seven years when's
that gonna work for me when does the
pendulum swing the other way
you think when he's 90 and i'm 83
oh he's going down welcome to his bed
pinch a little tube not so tough now are
we hot shot huh
i'll knock those training pants right
off your
[Applause]
i've backside 77 years for this moment
oh you're going down and i'm gonna do
all the stuff to him that he used to do
to me my brother
used to make me hit myself anybody ever
lived through that when
when you feel more useless than when
you're pummeling yourself with your own
fist you know
over and over he's doing it and in my
mind i'm thinking you know instead of
like i'm thinking i should be thinking
like how do i stop this but in my mind
i'm going
you should i open my hand or shut it
which would hurt less
should i punch myself or should i slap
myself
and my dad would finally come leave
alone i'm not doing it he's doing to
himself
but okay then
his favorite thing to do we've all been
through this whether you have an older
sibling or not he grabbed my underwear
from behind remember this trick
how far do they pull that up about 80
maybe 90 times farther than you could
ever imagine the extension on anything
every day and every day i'm walking back
into the house trying to dig it out
neighbors are looking out the window i
think the boy across the street's got
worms
i think he's got an older brother his
underwear is over his ears cut him some
slack
see my brother knew exactly how far the
underwear would stretch
because it used to be his anybody know
what i'm talking about
that's something to look forward to when
you're five
growing into your brother's underwear
they say can't wait to fit into those
babies
come on off with them partner i've got
plans
of course by the time i got them there's
no elastic left at all
so my dad would get clever for one of
those chip clips on the back of me to
keep him tight on me kind of
embarrassing having that sack of cheetos
dangling off the seat of your pants but
you know what
they stay fresh i think that's what's
most important
it's funny that my mom never remembered
history in the way that it happened she
didn't remember
the cruelty of my brother and it's funny
because we talk about that and like i
said before
you feel like you're turning into a
different person as you get older
anybody here feel like you're starting
to turn into your own parents even
though you probably said you wouldn't
that first feeling you get when you
start saying something to your kids
that they said to you and it's it's like
throwing up it's like being physically
ill
it's like you don't want this coming out
of your mouth but here it comes can't
stop it it feels horrible when it does
yeah
listen to me when you live under this
roof you go oh god
you go by these rules
[Applause]
you know what i said the other day i'm
not proud of this i actually use the
term
roughhousing that's like from the 40s
right who even says that say you've had
us there's a supper with the town fool
they're rough housing or someone's
liable to slap you right the puss
knock it off the rough housing fear
they'll throw their river that's what
they'll do you're gonna have the dna and
you're gonna sing see
so here's what you do to not turn into
your parents or at least hold it off for
a little while
you got to keep fighting with them you
got to get natural to disagree with your
parents because once you start agreeing
with them then you're them
from the perspective of the parent once
you have a child your job is to turn
that person into you
you don't know it at the time but that's
your job and you're on it might take 30
years it might take 40 might take 50 but
you did it you turned them into you
now they're you a younger you we don't
need you and you die do you understand
how life works
you have to keep aggravating your
parents to keep everyone alive longer i
used to call my mom just to tell her i
was doing things that she never let me
do when i lived with her that was the
most fun i could ever have
just give her a call middle of the week
hey mom how are you yeah doing great
just want to let you know
i'm having fruity pebbles for dinner i
don't know if that bothers you at all
but i have whipped cream on top of him
and i'm eating him in the living room
with no shirt on
and every light in this house is on
right now too
i also have the heat on and the door's
open i don't even care
when the refrigerator is open i'm not
even using it i just leave it open all
the
it's actually fighting the heater and
i'm sitting really far back in my chair
with my eyes crossed
i'm cracking my knuckles a little bit
later we're going to have relay races
with scissors you might want to stop by
around six
for the relay races with scissors it was
all her hot buttons in one one phone
call
especially the fruity pebbles the cocoa
pebbles my mom would never buy us though
she always buys the fake ones you know
i'm talking about the
generic ones that don't even come in a
box they come in a bag like a giant yard
waste leaf bag full of
generic who could eat them and even if
they were the good ones much less those
you don't even realize until you get
those home there is no place in your
house that you can fit that bag it's
this big you
you can't bend it in half it rips
there's pebbles all over the floor like
the ants won't even eat them that's how
horrible they are like the ants
will crawl over the generic cocoa
pebbles in defiance like i'm not eating
man you eat it
you know the cereal's awful when it's
all over the kitchen floor and the dog
just kind of walks by and goes ah
probably going to take a pass on those
if you don't mind
there's so many of those generic
varieties every good cereal has that
generic brother you know what i'm saying
like fruit loops fruit loops has like 60
of them
see what i got you these are fruit hoops
their fruit rings fruit rounds fruit
circles fruit o's fruit donuts fruit
tires
they've all got it those aren't lucky
charms they're fortuitous trinkets
that's exactly what those are and at
least that one's kind of clever right
cause then they got lazy
and they just started switching the
words around to make it generic like
take a cereal with two words
flip it around now it's generic flakes
of corn
there are flakes of corn crisps of rice
combs of honey puffs of wheat
crunch of captains cry what that doesn't
even make sense
crunch of captains but that one is my
favorite
even as an adult still eat captain
crunch can't eat it like i used to
though
i get like one box a month that's all i
can handle takes at least three weeks
for the roof of my mouth to heal after
the first container
who's that made out of gravel
captain crunch i ever see him i'm taking
him down it's like this big in real life
that includes the hat so he's really
small
well here's where i'm going with this if
you're a kid and your parents always
bought you the generic cereal and you
kept riding them sooner or later they'd
break
and buy you a box of the real stuff this
doesn't mean you won
it just means they want to have that box
so they can refill it with the stuff
from the bag is essentially what they're
doing there
what are you telling your own kids
you're saying you're so stupid i could
put kibbles and bits in this package
and you would eat it because toucan sam
is on the front of it
but guess what kids are smart enough to
know that the cereal's been switched
they know if the box has been around for
a while think of the dumbest family
you've ever known right
even they'll figure it out sooner or
later how many generations before one
kid realizes
that the cereal box in front of him is
older than he is right
hey with those wheaties billy oh they're
great didn't
realize that lou gehrig had been
reactivated for this season that's
a plus good for the game as far as i'm
concerned
yeah my mom bought us all the cheap
stuff and it was before the era
of those stores where everything cost a
dollar that became her favorite store at
the end
you have those around here everything is
that she'll go in there with 20 bucks
and just tear that place up
to leave a path of destruction in her
wake and then feel compelled to show me
everything she bought there one miracle
greater than the last
it's like look at this do you believe i
got this at the dollar store
and i'm like yes actually i do
it's an oven mitt i wouldn't even know
where else to look for one
plus i was with you when you bought it
so yes i believe you got it at the
dollar store
you always look to buy people's stuff in
the dollar store too big heart she'd be
in there go oh my god you know i'd love
that your sister would love one of those
but you're right she would because i
just talked to her this morning she said
she wants an emergency poncho i'm not
even kidding
she's like if you talk to mom would you
hint that i would like an emergency
poncho
because i don't have a dollar i'll see
what i can do i
i can't guarantee anything but i might
be able to swing this deal for you
so i had to tell her in a nice way stop
buying people gifts at the dollar store
i know you mean well but knock it off
here's what you do
just give them a dollar tell them it's a
dollar store certificate right that way
think of what they want we don't know
what other people like it that maybe
they don't want the pot holder or the
air freshener maybe they like the pizza
cutter or the corn skewers or the ice
cube tray or the
12-pack of sponges or the army men or
the marbles or the you know hasselhoff
cd we don't know what other people like
not for us to decide there's some great
stuff in there too
ever see something in a dollar store
that actually cost less than a dollar
what went horribly wrong there they
couldn't move it for a buck now they're
really slashing prices
here's what i saw and i'm not even
kidding i saw cassette tapes
in a dollar store for 88 cents
how many things wrong with that sentence
first off we don't use cassettes anymore
hence the reduction in price
but i got to be honest i couldn't stop
looking at them i was fascinated it was
like memory lane
and then i thought man i hate to be one
of those singers wouldn't that be
horrible
how'd you like to be that guy you're the
guy whose tape
cost 88 cents
your tape costs less than a blank tape
you know what i'm saying like people are
paying more money for tapes with nothing
on them at all
in fact your voice is making the tape
worth less
you're devaluing a cassette tape by
singing because the blank tape cost a
dollar
so the value of your voice is negative
12 cents
i don't buy a lot of things in that
store but i do buy one thing and let me
pass this along to you as advice
never get your sunglasses anywhere but a
dollar store because we all know that
formula the more money you pay
for sunglasses the sooner they're going
to be gone from your life whether you
lose them break them whatever the more
you pay sooner they're gone once in my
life i broke my own rule
i spent a good amount of money on a pair
of sunglasses on the way home from
making that purchase
on the way home wanted to change lanes
did that thing where you
pop your head out the window they blew
off my face at about 65 miles an hour
i can still see them in the rearview
mirror and over and no it's like in slow
motion no
the pair that i bought nine years ago at
the dollar store not a scratch on them
today they're mints
you can't get rid of them even when you
want to get rid of them one time i
thought we lost them was this summer we
were on vacation we're at one of those
water parks and i got off one of the
slides and i reached up
on my head and i didn't feel them and we
all had a big laugh oh i guess i lost my
dollar glasses what are we gonna do now
we got home from the trip glasses
they're on my front step i'm not even
kidding
with a note this isn't over that really
actually happened
psycho glasses
you ever in a store like that and you
hear music playing you don't really pay
any attention to it then the music stops
and everybody hears the voice
out of nowhere i'm in a dollar store
also this guy goes you're listening to
the dollar tree radio network
really oh how far down the radio pole
did he have to slide to
wind up with that sweet gig
he's the disc jockey at the dollar store
how can they afford that
point is they can't afford it he's
probably like the assistant manager and
the radio personality
and he's like stocking shelves waiting
for the song dan then he runs in the
back room and grabs the microphone
all right let's get the freeze pops
about six high over
charlie pride kiss and angel good
morning and love it like the devil want
to get back home it's 8 15 15 minutes
after 8 o'clock cloudy skies and 74
degrees
hey it's going crazy back there on aisle
six because we've got spaghettios on
sale
they're three to a box and you guessed
it one dollar
here's cheap trick
still can't believe they had cassette
tapes in that place
one of the cassettes was by a
ventriloquist
it's an audio tape how good does he have
to be
he really doesn't even need a puppet
when you think about it
that's how weird that is believe me i
have seen a lot of ventriloquists in all
the years that i've been doing this and
i have come to the conclusion
that a bad ventriloquist is more
entertaining than a good one
okay truthfully a bad ventriloquist
actually challenges his audience to
become ventriloquists themselves
i saw this guy he was so horrible people
in the audience turned to each other
going this guy's terrible
i can't believe how burn describe this
when is it going to be done
and if the dollar store is a little too
expensive for you here's my mom's other
favorite thing especially this time of
year loved to go to the garage sales oh
loved him and i would go with her and i
was just fascinated more than anything
not so much at the items but the prices
of the items how do they come up with
these prices yeah
i saw a puzzle for eight cents how does
that happen
what do they have a meeting the night
before the kitchen table they're all
sitting around all right what are we
gonna do on the puzzle any thoughts
well i don't know that it's dime-worthy
but there is no way i'm letting that go
for a nickel
tell you what let's throw eight at them
see what happens
secretly we'll accept six but that
doesn't leave this room can we all agree
that
secretly will accept six
kind of like the goodwill store that's
like a garage sale that never closes
i'll tell you why i love goodwill
because there is stuff in there you
couldn't imagine someone buying once
even that's what i love about the
goodwill
weirdest thing i ever saw in a goodwill
store it was a whole shelf of them
trophies take a minute
how pathetic would your life have to be
to buy a trophy at a goodwill store
that's pretty much waving the white flag
as a sportsman isn't it
kind of brings giving up to a whole new
level when you're decorating your mantle
with someone else's athletic
achievements isn't it
somehow you're proud of it you're
showing it off to people this
no to be honest i don't even know how to
swim
i just thought it would look great next
to my arby's employee of the year award
from 1987.
no i never even worked there i just
think it's fantastic
looks great next to the trophy doesn't
it
who can tell me what the most uh popular
item is at secondhand stores anyone that
is based on a season that's the clue
that i will give you
christmas sweaters would be number two
halloween costume very good does that
come from you sir
have you ever done that bought halloween
costume at the goodwill no but you've
seen it happen right
and by saying it it's make your costume
out of the things they have not buy an
old halloween costume because
no one would do that they're not made
well enough to get a second spin plus
they make them so well who would buy an
old halloween really remember the ones
that we had to wear the one-dimensional
plastic face mask that fasted with a
rubber band that would snap off your
face
after the second house because the metal
piece would flip sideways and shoot
through the hole and you can't get a
back so you're
trying to stretch it under the staple
and get it through the hole but that
doesn't work because there's a tear
where the hole is
so you're like holding up the mask with
one hand and dragging the candy with the
other you're knocking on doors with your
rear end yeah this is working out
perfectly
i've got a box of milk duds i'm ready to
pass out this is not an exciting day
i'm gonna go home and get my ghost
costume
remember the ghost costume that was our
insurance policy right
fallback option if all else failed you
could always be a ghost he's right there
on the bed waiting for you that's how
easy that is
pull up that sheet you drop it overhead
you're a ghost
i've always spot the bedwetters a lot
quicker on halloween too couldn't you
thank god we look at that
a specter with a bladder control problem
i'm doubly frightened
but hopefully you never have to use the
fallback option because whatever your
kids want to be for halloween that's the
costume you get them when i was a kid
i was batman every year because i was
such a huge fan of of batman and kids
now
that's more popular even when i was a
kid but it's so different now because
kids dress up like batman
they've got body armor on and remember
our batman
like from all adam west was our batman
right that's how i thought batman was
supposed to behave i was knocking on
doors i wasn't just batman i was adam
west
as batman right
trick or treat good citizen
carefully produce your sugar
coated confections
and place them in the candy superb of my
utility building
sure it took me a little longer to trick
or treat but i was i was method
anybody ever go too late the costume
that your son or daughter asked you for
wasn't there anymore
then you got to literally scrape
whatever's at the bottom of the barrel
the whole ride home you're like okay how
do i sell this
as the intended costume how am i to
convince an eight-year-old boy
that holly hobby is an appropriate look
you're like
no it looks fantastic just uh stick
close to your brother's strawberry
shortcake everything's going to be fine
because halloween is about disguise and
then you have to give your kids the
rules of halloween remember those rules
of halloween
number one was the apple rule it was
that somebody gave you an apple you had
to
consider the possibility of what exactly
right that some nut
may have put a razor blade in the apple
it is then your responsibility and i
mean this
to whip that apple off the side of that
guy's house as hard as you possibly can
it's one of the unwritten laws of
halloween like the one that says if you
put a pumpkin out in front of your house
may as well put with it a sign that says
hey would you guys please kick this all
over the neighborhood please we were
we were hoping you'd have a punting
contest with it out front and then
smear the what's left of the
jack-o-lantern all over our siding we'd
like that
those are the same people but all their
candy one big bowl right
leave it on the front step what does air
sign say anyone
take one where do you live take one are
you serious
i'm the first kid of that house i'm
taking the bowl too
i've got a decorative mother's day gift
as far as i'm concerned
take one you're an idiot take one how
about the guy that forgot halloween
remember that guy didn't have any idea
what day it was no candy
you get there now he has to find things
in the house to give you yeah that
always worked out well didn't it
slim gems and robitussin no that's
perfect my
bronchitis here kid here's an egg
scoop of peanut butter for you my friend
man if the guy next door has bread what
a day this should be
but a boy can dream
[Applause]
i was talking about bad weather earlier
there's a reason why i hate cold weather
and you guys get a lot of snow here
right a lot of ice a lot of horrible
driving conditions last winter i i
almost wrecked my car i was i
i was couldn't control the direction
that my car was moving it was sliding
from one side to the next
and at that very moment i had this
flashback to driver's ed in high school
remember they taught you any old films
how to drive in the ice when your
car starts to slide steer from the
direction of the skid
that's great i'm just kidding towards an
oncoming semi truck
bring it on
it's weird philosophies it's like saying
if somebody shoots you
move in the direction of the bullet
after you've been stabbed fall directly
on the knife
[Laughter]
that guy narrated every film i ever saw
in high school
look at that guy my favorites were the
anti-drug films that they made and
that's a good message keep the kids off
drugs problem was they never changed
that film
they just kept showing it was made in
1953 and every generation that came
there after
had to watch the same film over and over
black and white
kid with the buzz cut
billy got mixed up with the wrong
bunch of boys they want billy to
sample marijuana careful bill
it's the devil
billy succumbs to peer pressure and
underestimates the power of the
evil weed
look out bill you can't stop that
locomotive with your face
too bad for bill
true story uh
flew in here uh uh last night no problem
there and a lot all the years i've
tried every different type of
transportation to get from
gig to gig and uh my least memorable
least favorite
was a traveling greyhound how many of us
here ever been on a greyhound bus any of
us most of us at some point how you
doing right here
what is your name landon like michael
landon
is that right where did you go landon
what were points a and b on this
greyhound
dallas texas houston from dallas to
houston okay
uh having not ever made that trip you're
in your car landon
how long is it going to take you to get
from dallas to houston you're driving
about three and a half okay now let me
guess uh greyhound
six days seven nights give or take yeah
yeah plus it's fun because you get to
ride next to every psycho mutant loser
freak that ever lived
where do they get those people you ever
look around yourself where are they get
them folks we're gonna be swinging by
the carnival picking up the staff on our
way to houston so
uh if you don't mind sharing an armrest
with tilt-a-whirl gym we'll be up and
running at about three hours
my trip uh i guess uh probably longer
than yours but trust me both long enough
it was a one-way experience
from cleveland ohio to chicago and uh
it's three o'clock in the morning when i
board the bus
to make things even more fun 3 a.m i've
got two objectives on this bus one is to
get home
the other how about sleep along the way
that's all friendly
greyhound driver apparently didn't want
me to sleep
got in his microphone started talking
wouldn't shut up scariest night of my
life
three in the morning just want to sleep
we're heading out here
yeah welcome my boy greyhound birth
number one
one one seven we should be arriving in
chicago approximately
10 30 a.m the bathrooms are located in
the far rear of the bus if you have to
use them for any reason
also the smoking areas in the last three
rows of the bus
if they got children on the bus would
you please keep my seat next to you with
the seat belt securely fastened
in your lap if you're going to be
totally come on shut up i want to sleep
all right
i know how to ride a bus i've done it
before
so i dozed off for about 30 minutes 45
tops
i wake up somewhere in the middle of
ohio he's like
because marriage
is a big step
you all got to decide you're going to
dedicate yourself to one person
for the rest of your life what the
hell's he talking about stop it
stop talking about it
slept most of the way to this day a
mystery how just remember waking up
six hours later somewhere fairly close
to home six hours later
still talking hasn't skipped a beat
trick or treating with always fun by my
house
sip we all never seem to get none of the
candy we
wanted we was always hoping for stuff
like
snicker bar
peanut butter cooks
whoppers and junior men snow
capped razor neck goopers slow poke
milk
red hot smarty sweet tart
hydromic good and plenty good and fruity
starbucks
now
jolly rancher marathon milky way
pre-musketeer bar hershey with nuts
chunky with raisins chuckles theater
honey paydays eggnog
powerhouse milkshake sugar babies
skittles bite size fruit juice
charleston chew glock bar mars bar
bun bar twix bar i'm enjoy
mounds eminem's reese's pieces
jujubes necco circus peanuts
chicklets hershey kisses jawbreakers
rollo
zero
laffy taffy bubblicious symphony special
dark
oh henry mr good bar nestle crunch at
fifth avenue
outrageous mary janes heath bars crackle
bars thoughts
[Applause]
and search with redson
but we'd always end up getting like
religious pamphlets
instead
[Laughter]
popcorn balls
and the apples with razor blade on the
outside
you guys are very nice thanks so much
you